Guide to the Barney Rosset papers,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series II: Chronological Materials, 1879-2005
  - 1962
    - Grove Bibliography (Box 4, Folder 95)
      - Borges, Jorge Luis--Ficciones (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Burroughs, William--Naked Lunch (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - Clurman, Harold, ed.--Seven Plays of the Modern Theater (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - Genet, Jean--The Screens (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - Garten, H.F.--Modern German Drama (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - Gover, Robert--"One Hundred Dollars Misunderstanding" (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - Hitler, Adolf--Hitler's Secret Book (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - Hortelano, Juan Garcia--Summer Storm (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Rechy, John--City of Night (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Robbe-Grillet, Alain--Last Year at Marienbad (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Grove Press Consolidated Financial Statements (December ) (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence
      - January (Box 5, Folder 12)
      - February (Box 5, Folder 13)
      - March (Box 5, Folder 14)
      - April (Box 5, Folder 15)
      - May (Box 5, Folder 16)
      - June (Box 5, Folder 17)
      - July (Box 5, Folder 18)
      - August (Box 5, Folder 19)
      - September (Box 5, Folder 20)
      - October (Box 5, Folder 21)
      - November (Box 5, Folder 22)
      - December (with clippings) (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - 1963
    - Grove Bibliography (Box 5, Folder 24)
      - Genet, Jean--Our Lady of the Flowers (Box 5, Folder 25)
      - Harris, Frank--My Life and Loves (Box 5, Folder 26)
      - Johnson, Uwe--Speculations About Jacob (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Financial (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Italian Preface to--The Subterraneans (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence
      - January (Box 5, Folder 30)
      - February (Box 5, Folder 31)
      - March (Box 5, Folder 32)
      - April (Box 5, Folder 33)
      - May (Box 5, Folder 34)
      - June (Box 5, Folder 35)
      - July (Box 5, Folder 36)
      - August (Box 5, Folder 37)
      - September --w/ "Doctor Martin Smiles" by William S. Burroughs (Box 5, Folder 38)
      - October (Box 5, Folder 39)
      - November (Box 5, Folder 40)
      - December (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - 1964
    - Grove Bibliography (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Beckett/ FILM/ "I Am Curious" (Grove Press Interview) (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Grove Bibliography
      - Beckett, Samuel--How It Is (Box 5, Folder 44)
      - Berne, Eric--Games People Play (Box 5, Folder 45)
      - Burroughs, William S.--Nova Express (Box 5, Folder 46)
      - Doss, Margaret Patterson--San Francisco at Your Feet (Box 5, Folder 47)
      - Genet, Jean--The Thief's Journal (Box 5, Folder 48)
      - Hochhuth, Rolf--The Deputy (Box 5, Folder 49)
      - Selby Jr., Hubert--Last Exit to Brooklyn (Box 5, Folder 50)
      - Semprun, Jorge--The Long Voyage (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - Financial (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - Cardozo Life Interview, Fall 1998 (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - Correspondence
      - January --w/ Freedom of Information Act Materials (Box 5, Folder 54)
      - February (Box 5, Folder 55)
      - April (Box 5, Folder 56)
      - May (Box 5, Folder 57)
      - June (Box 5, Folder 58)
      - July (Box 5, Folder 59)
      - August (Box 5, Folder 60)
      - September (Box 5, Folder 61)
      - October --w/ Legal Dispute (Naked Lunch) Materials/ Olympia Reader Disputes (Box 5, Folder 62)
      - November --w/ Freedom of Information Act Materials (Box 5, Folder 63)
      - December --w/ Freedom of Information Act Materials (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - 1965
    - Grove Press Authors (Box 5, Folder 65)
    - Grove Bibliography (Box 5, Folder 66)
      - Anthology of Chinese Literature (Box 5, Folder 67)
      - Brautigan, Richard--A Confederate General from Big Sur (Box 5, Folder 68)
      - Elsner, Gisela--The Giant Dwarfs (Box 5, Folder 69)
      - Fanon, Frantz--The Wretched of the Earth (Box 5, Folder 70)
      - The Olympia Reader (Box 5, Folder 71)
      - The Autobiography of Malcolm X (Box 5, Folder 72)
    - Financial (Box 5, Folder 73)
    - Condensed Correspondence
      - January (2 folders) (Box 5, Folder 74-75)
      - February (Box 5, Folder 76)
      - March (Box 5, Folder 77)
      - April (Box 5, Folder 78)
      - May (Box 5, Folder 79)
      - June (Box 5, Folder 80)
      - July (Box 5, Folder 81)
      - August (Box 5, Folder 82)
      - September --w/ Press Releases and Freedom of Information Act Materials (Box 5, Folder 83)
      - October (Box 5, Folder 84)
      - November --w/ Evergreen Review clippings (Box 5, Folder 85)
      - December (Box 5, Folder 86)
  - 1966
    - Bibliography (Box 5, Folder 87)
      - Duras, Marguerite The Ravishing of Lol Stein (Box 5, Folder 88)
      - Pinter, Harold The Homecoming (Box 5, Folder 89)
    - Financial (Box 5, Folder 90)
    - Condensed Correspondence
      - January (Box 5, Folder 91)
      - February (Box 5, Folder 92)
      - March (Box 5, Folder 93)
      - April (Box 5, Folder 94)
        - Henry Miller Evergreen Review Article "George Grosz' Ecco Homo" (Box 5, Folder 95)
      - April (Box 5, Folder 96)
      - May (Box 5, Folder 97)
      - June (Box 5, Folder 98)
        - Royalties and Inventory, William S. Burroughs (Box 5, Folder 99)
      - July --w/ Freedom of Information Act Materials (Box 5, Folder 100)
      - August (Box 5, Folder 101)
      - September --w/ Freedom of Information Act Materials (Box 5, Folder 102)
      - October --w/ Freedom of Information Act Materials (Box 5, Folder 103)
      - November --w/ Freedom of Information Act Materials (Box 5, Folder 104)
      - December --w/ Freedom of Information Act Materials (Box 5, Folder 105)
  - 1967
    - "Grove Press Inc.: Interim Report to Shareholders, Six Months Ended June 30, 1967" Pamphlet (Box 5, Folder 106)
    - Grove Bibliography (Box 5, Folder 107)
      - Cover Photocopies of Evergreen Review February, Ferdydurke, and Black Skin, White Masks (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Grove Bibliography Annotated (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Financial
      - Grove Press, Inc. Consolidated Statement of Income and Retained Earnings (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - Grove Press Annual Report 1967 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Condensed
      - Correspondence, Announcements, and Freedom of Information Act Materials (semi-chronological), (2 folders) (Box 6, Folder 5-6)
  - 1968
    - Grove Bibliography (Box 6, Folder 7)
      - Annotated Covers and Copies (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Financial
      - Grove Press, Inc. Consolidated Statement of Income and Retained Earnings (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Oe Letter, Undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Condensed Correspondence
      - Interviews Notated (Box 6, Folder 11)
      - January
        - Jonas, Gerald "The Story of Grove" New York Times Magazine (Box 6, Folder 12)
        - Correspondence, Announcements, Articles, and Freedom of Information Act Materials (Box 6, Folder 13)
      - February (Box 6, Folder 14)
      - March (Box 6, Folder 15)
        - Liss, Joe "Notes for the Bolivian Trip on a Day to Day Basis" (Box 6, Folder 16)
      - April (Box 6, Folder 17)
      - May --w/ Evergreen Review Copy and Kenzaburo Oe Material (Box 6, Folder 18)
      - June --w/ Freedom of Information Act Material (Box 6, Folder 19)
      - July --w/ "Bomb Explodes at Grove Press" New York Times Article (Box 6, Folder 20)
        - Conversation with Arafat Evergreen Review No. 56 (Box 6, Folder 21)
        - Peace-Mendes France Evergreen Review No. 56 (Box 6, Folder 22)
      - August (Box 6, Folder 23)
      - September (Box 6, Folder 24)
      - October --w/ Grove Press Bombing and CIA Lawsuit Articles (Box 6, Folder 25)
      - December (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - 1969
    - "Pentagonism, a Substitute for Imperialism" by Juan Bosch, Book Advertisement on Ramparts (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Bibliography
      - Cover Art and Copy Copies (Box 6, Folder 28)
      - Grove Press News Release, "For Immediate Release Grove Press to Produce Video Magazine for HomeViewing" (Box 6, Folder 29)
      - Inventory (Box 6, Folder 30)
      - Antonioni, Michelangelo--L'Avventura (Box 6, Folder 31)
      - Fidel Castro Speaks (Box 6, Folder 32)
      - Garaudy, Roger--The Crisis in Communism (Box 6, Folder 33)
      - Murton and Hyams--Accomplices to the Crime (Box 6, Folder 34)
      - The New Left Reader--w/ "Nativity Scene" by George de Stefano (The Nation, 2000) (Box 6, Folder 35)
      - Shaw, Robert--The Man in the Glass Booth (Box 6, Folder 36)
      - Tyler, Parker--Underground Film (Box 6, Folder 37)
      - Tynan, Kenneth--Oh! Calcutta! And "How to Publish 'Dirty Books' for Fun and Profit" by Martin May er (Saturday Evening Post ) (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Groves Press Annual Report (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Grove Press College Catalog (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Condensed Correspondence (Interviews Notated) (Box 6, Folder 41)
      - January (Box 6, Folder 42)
      - February (Box 6, Folder 43)
      - March--w/ Grove Press Complimentary Copy Cards (copies) (Box 6, Folder 44)
      - April -June (Box 6, Folder 45)
      - August --w/ "The Old Smut Peddler" Life Magazine (Box 6, Folder 46)
      - September --w/ Freedom of Information Act Materials (Box 6, Folder 47)
      - October (Box 6, Folder 48)
      - November (Box 6, Folder 49)
      - December --w/ Freedom of Information Act Materials (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - 1970
    - Bibliography
      - "I Am Curious" Advertisements (Box 6, Folder 51)
      - Grove Press Cloth and Paperback Book Sales Catalog Fall-Winter 1970/1971 (Box 6, Folder 52)
      - Grove Inventory (Box 6, Folder 53)
      - Suttler, David, IV-F: AGuide toDraft Exemption (Box 6, Folder 54)
    - Financial
      - Dun & Bradstreet Analytical Report of Grove Press (December 31, 1968-December 31, 1970)-also CIA Document #71, "Released" August 29, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 55)
    - Kenzaburo Oe Poem (Box 6, Folder 56)
    - Correspondence
      - January --w/ Freedom of Information Act Materials (Box 6, Folder 57)
      - February--w/ Freedom of Information Act Materials (Box 6, Folder 58)
      - March--w/ Freedom of Information Act Materials (Box 6, Folder 59)
      - April --w/ Freedom of Information Act Materials, Condensed/Notated Interviews, Articles related to Grove Occupation, (3 folders) (Box 6, Folder 60-2)
      - May --w/ Union and Women's Liberation Arbitration and Leaflets; and Robin Morgan Interview: "She is the Wickedest Witch and She Hates Men" (Box 6, Folder 63)
      - June --w/ Freedom of Information Act Materials, Village Voice Announcement of Evergreen Review Resignation (Box 6, Folder 64)
      - July --w/ "Barney Rosset: Taboo Guru"Screw, Freedom of Information Act Materials, "Women's Glib" Village Voice (Box 6, Folder 65)
      - August --w/ Draft of "Joint Statement of FLM Joint Board and Grove Press, Inc." (Box 6, Folder 66)
      - September --w/ "Pornography: Bluest Chip" by Carol Matthews New York Post Financial Section (Box 6, Folder 67)
      - October --w/ Telegram to Samuel Beckett from Barney Rosset and Dick Seaver, and "Text of Nixon's Statement Rejecting the Report of the Obscenity Panel" New York Times (Box 6, Folder 68)
      - November --w/ Freedom of Information Act Materials (Box 6, Folder 69)
      - December --w/ Freedom of Information Act Materials, and "Big Headlines, Small Profits: Grove Press is Certainly Curious" The Spotlight (Box 6, Folder 70)
  - 1971
    - Bibliography (Box 6, Folder 71)
    - Grove Press Books Paperback and Cloth Books Sales Catalog, Spring-Summer (Box 6, Folder 72)
    - General Correspondence (Box 6, Folder 73)
    - Financial/ Freedom of Information Act Accounting of Grove (Box 6, Folder 74)
    - Correspondence
      - January -February (Box 6, Folder 75)
      - March-April (Box 6, Folder 76)
      - May -June --w/ Freedom of Information act Materials, Contracts, "Memories as Weapons" Time (Box 6, Folder 77)
      - July -August --w/ Freedom of Information Act Materials, and "Stage: Hand of Pinter" by Clive Barnes New York Times (Box 6, Folder 78)
      - September --w/ Freedom of Information Act Materials, Valerie Solanis Trial Subpoena, and "No Thanks for the Memory" Life (Box 6, Folder 79)
      - October to December --w/ "Payments to De Grazia" (Box 6, Folder 80)
  - 1972
    - Bibliography 1972 (Box 6, Folder 81)
    - "Shapiro-Haley Malcolm X" (Condensed Interviews) (Box 6, Folder 82)
    - Financial
      - Dun & Bradstreet Analytical Report of Grove Press (December 31, 1968-December 31, 1970)-also CIA Document #71, "Released" August 29, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 83)
      - Freedom of Information Act Grove Accounting (Box 6, Folder 84)
    - Correspondence
      - January (Box 6, Folder 85)
      - February (Box 6, Folder 86)
      - Marchand April (Box 6, Folder 87)
      - May --w/ "The Bizarre New World of Jorge Borges"Kansas City Star, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 88)
    - June -August (Box 6, Folder 89)
    - September -December --w/ Freedom of Information Act Files, and "Grove Press Sues to Cut Link with Random House" New York Times (Box 6, Folder 90)
  - 1973
    - "Description of Business (From Annual Report 1973)" (Box 6, Folder 91)
    - Bibliography (Box 6, Folder 92)
      - Grove Press Fall 1973 Sales Catalog (Box 6, Folder 93)
      - Grove Press 1973 Sales Catalog as Distributed by Random House (2 copies) (Box 6, Folder 94)
      - Grove Press Annual Report 1973 (Box 6, Folder 95)
    - Formentor Prize File, "The Second Date of Ramon Mercador" Article (Box 6, Folder 96)
    - Condensed Correspondence
      - January --w/ Freedom of Information Act Materials (Box 6, Folder 97)
      - February (Box 6, Folder 98)
      - March (Box 6, Folder 99)
      - April (Box 6, Folder 100)
      - May --w/ "A Tribute to Grove Press" Film Exhibition Articles and Pamphlet Copies (Box 6, Folder 101)
      - July (Box 6, Folder 102)
      - August (w/ Clippings) (Box 6, Folder 103)
      - September (Box 6, Folder 104)
      - October (Box 6, Folder 105)
      - November (Box 6, Folder 106)
      - December (w/ some November ) (Box 6, Folder 107)
  - 1974/1975
    - Binder Front Matter--Correspondence with Michael E. Uslan (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - 1974
    - Bibliography (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - Peyrefitte, Roger Manouche (Copy and Photo of Cover Art and front Jacket Copy) (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - Beckett, Samuel--Mercier and Camier (Box 7, Folder 4)
      - Biely, Andrey--The Silver Dove (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Grove Press Spring 1974 Sales Catalog (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Grove Press Fall 1974 Sales Catalog (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Financial
      - Grove Press Annual Report 1974 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence
      - January -March (Box 7, Folder 9)
      - April -July (Box 7, Folder 10)
      - August -November (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - 1975
    - Bibliography (Box 7, Folder 12)
      - Antonioni, Michelangelo--The Passenger (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Grove Press Spring 1975 Sales Catalog (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Grove Press Fall 1975 Sales Catalog (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Financial
      - Grove Press Annual Report 1975 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence
      - March-April, and Undated (Box 7, Folder 17)
      - May -December --w/ "In Memory Sarah Greenbaum" (Box 7, Folder 18)
      - Joan Mitchell, Undated (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - 1976
    - Bibliography (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Grove Press Spring 1975 Sales Catalog (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Grove Press Fall 1975 Sales Catalog (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Bibliography
      - Lery, Howard and David Miller--Going to Jail (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Financial
      - Grove Press Annual Report 1976 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Condensed
      - January -December Correspondence and Excerpts from John Nathan's Introduction to Teach Us to Outgrow Our Madness: Four Short Novels by Kenzaburo Öe (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - 1977-1978
    - Bibliography (Box 7, Folder 26)
      - Grove Press Spring 1977 Sales Catalog (Box 7, Folder 27)
      - Grove Press Fall 1977 Sales Catalog (Box 7, Folder 28)
      - Exner, Judith--My Story (Box 7, Folder 29)
      - Gervasi, Tom--Arsenal of Democracy (Box 7, Folder 30)
      - Oe, Kenzaburo--Teach Us to Outgrow Our Madness (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Financial
      - Grove Press Annual Report 1977 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Condensed (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - 1977 Correspondence, (2 folders) (Box 7, Folder 33-34)
    - Bibliography (Box 7, Folder 35)
      - Grove Press Spring 1978 Catalog (Box 7, Folder 36)
      - Grove Press Fall 1978 Catalog (Box 7, Folder 37)
      - Chamberlain, Elwyn M.--Gates of Fire (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Financial
      - Grove Press Annual Report 1978 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Condensed
      - January -June Correspondence and "Chicago JDL Chief: He Hits Without Hate" Chicago Sun Times June 12, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Buzz Alpert (Barney Rosset Cousin) Articles (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - June -December 1978 Correspondence (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - 1979
    - Calvin Israel Correspondence (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Bibliography (Box 7, Folder 44)
      - Grove Press Fall 1979 Sales Catalog (Box 7, Folder 45)
      - Grove Press Spring 1979 Sales Catalog (Box 7, Folder 46)
      - Derogy, Jacques and Hesi Carmel--The Untold Story of Israel (Box 7, Folder 47)
      - Malraux, André--Man's Hope (Box 7, Folder 48)
      - Odets, Clifford--Six Plays (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Condensed
      - January -July Correspondence and "Richard Seaver, Publisher" New York Times Book Review (Box 7, Folder 50)
      - Coburn, Randy Sue "Barney Rosset, the Force Behind Grove Press" The Washington Star (and partial copy of original) (Box 7, Folder 51)
      - August -December Correspondence and "One Hundred Dollar Misunderstanding (1962)" by Rober Gover (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - 1980
    - "Waiting for my Godot Father" Tatler Magazine (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - Bibliography
      - Grove Press Fall 1980 Sales Catalog (Box 7, Folder 54)
      - Bibliography (Box 7, Folder 55)
      - Thelwell, Michael--The Harder They Come (Box 7, Folder 56)
    - Grove Press Spring 1980 Catalog (Box 7, Folder 57)
    - Condensed
      - Notated Interviews (Box 7, Folder 58)
      - January -December 1980 Correspondence (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - 1981
    - Bibliography (Box 7, Folder 60)
      - Grove Press Fall 1981 Catalog (Box 7, Folder 61)
      - Buitrago, Ann Mari and Leon Andrew Immerman--Are You Now or Have You Ever Been in the FBI FilesÀ (Box 7, Folder 62)
      - Kennedy Toole, John--A Confederacy of Dunces (Box 7, Folder 63)
      - Grove Press Spring 1981 Catalog (Box 7, Folder 64)
    - Condensed
      - Notated Interviews (Box 7, Folder 65)
      - January -December Correspondence (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - 1982
    - Bibliography (Box 7, Folder 67)
    - Grove Press Spring 1982 Sales Catalog (Box 7, Folder 68)
    - Grove Press Fall 1982 Sales Catalog (Box 7, Folder 69)
    - Condensed (Box 7, Folder 69)
    - January -December 1982 Correspondence (Box 7, Folder 70)
  - 1983
    - Bibliography (Box 7, Folder 71)
      - Grove Press Fall 1983 Sales Catalog (Box 7, Folder 72)
      - Adler, Alfred--Souvenirs Fresh and Rancid (Box 7, Folder 73)
      - Rosset, Peter and John Vandermeer--The Nicaragua Reader (Box 7, Folder 74)
    - Ed De Grazia Interview with Eugene Ionesco (Box 7, Folder 75)
    - Condensed (Box 7, Folder 75)
    - January to December 1983 Correspondence and "Maurice Girodias: Perils of the Princely Pornographer" from Mavericks: Nine Independent Publishers (Box 7, Folder 76)
  - 1984
    - Bibliography and "Acid Dreams: The C.I.A., LSD, and Sixties Rebellion" by Martin A. Lee and Bruce Shlain (Box 7, Folder 77)
    - Bibliography
      - Grove Press Spring 1984 Sales Catalog (Box 7, Folder 78)
      - Grove Press Fall 1984 Catalog (Box 7, Folder 79)
    - Correspondence
      - Haskell Wexler Correspondence and Peter Israel (Box 7, Folder 80)
    - Condensed
      - Notated Interviews (Box 7, Folder 81)
      - January -June 1984 Correspondence (Box 7, Folder 82)
      - December 1984 Correspondence (Box 7, Folder 83)
  - 1985
    - "Paris Trip February1985" (Box 7, Folder 84)
    - Bibliography (Box 7, Folder 85)
      - Sellers, Terence--The Correct Sadist and Malcolm Bell's The Turkey Shoot (Box 7, Folder 86)
      - Grove Press Spring 1985 Catalog (Box 7, Folder 87)
    - Condensed
      - Notated Interviews and Milestones (Box 7, Folder 88)
      - January -July 1985 Correspondence (Box 7, Folder 89)
      - Interview of Jerome Lindon Aux Editions de Minuit (Box 7, Folder 90)
      - September -December 1985 Correspondence (Box 7, Folder 91)
      - Gontarski, S.E. "Censorship and the Literary Canon: The Rise and Fall of Grove Press" (Box 7, Folder 92)
  - 1986
    - Rosset, Barney "Publishing the New Novel from Three Decades of the French New Novel," Edited by Louis Oppenheim (Box 7, Folder 93)
    - Bibliography (Box 7, Folder 94)
    - Condensed
      - Notated Interviews (Box 7, Folder 95)
      - January to April 1986 Correspondence (Box 7, Folder 96)
      - "Panel of Beckett Scholars" Statements by Barney Rosset and Tom Bishop Introduction (Box 7, Folder 97)
    - April to August Correspondence and Assorted Rosset Articles and Interviews (Box 7, Folder 98)
    - September 1986 Manhattan, Inc., "Endgame" Seabrook, John (Box 7, Folder 99)
    - September 1986 Correspondence and "New York, New York" by Marie Nasta Manhattan Cooperator (October 1986) (Box 7, Folder 100)
    - October to December 1986 Correspondence (Box 7, Folder 101)
  - 1987
    - Rosset Comments at Hampshire College and January Correspondence (Box 7, Folder 102)
    - Condensed
      - Annotated Interviews and February-November Correspondence and Assorted Articles (Box 7, Folder 103)
    - Index on Censorship-November /December 1987-Vol. 16-No. 10 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - 1988
    - Correspondence and Assorted Articles (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - 1989
    - Notated Interviews and Assorted Articles (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - 1990
    - Assorted Articles and Correspondence, "Seven Days," and Speech from Sag Harbor Initiative on Censorshop (October 12, 1989) (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Notated Interviews (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Assorted Articles and Correspondence, (2 folders) (Box 8, Folder 6-7)
    - Condensed
      - Assorted 1990/1991 Articles (Copies and Originals) (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - 1991
    - The Evergreen Reader Spring--Binder Front Matter (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Grove Weidenfeld 1991 Academic and Backlist Catalog (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Publisher's Weekly, Copy of Cover (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Condensed
      - January -April 1991 Correspondence (Box 8, Folder 12)
      - May -December 1991 Correspondence and "The Write Stuff" by Eugene Palton The Peninsula Group Magazine (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - 1992
    - Barney to Annenberg School of Communications; Ed De Grazia Biography Outline (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Condensed
      - January -July 1992 Correspondence (Box 8, Folder 15)
      - August -December 1992 Correspondence and "Note by Barney Rosset, November 1992 About Teru Osato and Her Family" (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - 1993
    - Edward Beckett and S.E. Gontarski Correspondence (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - January -April Correspondence (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - May -December Correspondence (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - 1994
    - Binder Front Matter (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Assorted Correspondence and Front Matter (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - January -March (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - April -October (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - November -December (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - 1995
    - Assorted Correspondence and Articles
      - January and Undated (Box 8, Folder 24)
      - March-April (Box 8, Folder 25)
      - May -December (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - 1996
    - Assorted Articles and Correspondence (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - 1997
    - Assorted Articles, Correspondence, and Interviews, (2 folders) (Box 8, Folder 28-29)
  - 1998
    - "Barney Rosset's Italy Experience" and Feltrinelli-Labeled Separator (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - January -April 1998 Correspondence, Articles, and Interviews (Box 8, Folder 31)